tomandlorenzo2.blogspot.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | The Tom & Lorenzo Archives: 2006 -2011

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy provides information about the personal information that this website collects and the ways in which this website uses that personal information.

What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or participate in a contest. You may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.

What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

How do we protect your information?   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when we access your personal information. 

Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third Party Links   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Pennsylvania Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the Pennsylvania Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance   
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions of Use  
Please see our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://tomandlorenzo2.blogspot.com/2010/03/terms-and-conditions-of-use.html) page establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

Your Consent   
By using our website, you consent to our website privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Website: http://www.projectrungay.blogspot.com  
Email: tomandlorenzo @ gmail . com
